iphantom.com 2007-02-08

# Phantom Technologies

**iPhantom.com Privacy Statement**  
---  
   
Last updated: 04/25/2005  

Phantom Technologies LLC is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site www.iphantom.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.  
  
---|---  
  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our support team at [support@iphantom.com](mailto:support@iphantom.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

Welcome to the online Privacy Statement page for the iPhantom.com website. We take your privacy seriously and are committed to protecting your personal information while using our website.

We encourage you to review the privacy policies described below in this Privacy Statement. By visiting this website, you are consenting to the personal information practices described in this Privacy Statement.   
  
**Privacy Statement Index**  
|  |  Contact Information   
---|---  
|  Providing Users with Anonymous Access  
|  Collection of your Personal Information  
|  Use of your Personal Information  
|  Access to your Personal Information  
|  Security of your Personal Information  
|  Use of Cookies  
|  Protection of Children's Personal Information  
|  Joint or Co-Branded Products  
|  Enforcement of this Privacy Policy  
|  Changes to this Statement  
**Contact Information**  
  
This is the web site of **Phantom Technologies LLC.**  

Our postal address is:  
**5703 Oberlin Drive, Suite 106  
San Diego, CA 92121**

We can be reached via e-mail at [support@iphantom.com](mailto:support@iphantom.com)  
or you can reach us by telephone at **1.877.PHANTECH (742.6832)**  
  
Return to the top  
**Providing Users with Anonymous Access**  
You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.   
Return to the top  
**Collection of your Personal Information**  
  
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We do not log IP addresses of users that visit our site. 

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. 

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information, customer support, and/or order processing information. Order processing information that is collected through our website includes mailing and billing addresses, credit card information, and contact information such as e-mail and phone number that are used strictly for order confirmation purposes. 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our products, we will ask you for your friend’s name and e-mail address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time e-mail inviting him or her to visit our site for more information regarding the products. The e-mail will include a purchase code that may be used to receive a discount through the referral program. Phantom Technologies LLC or does not store the names or e-mail addresses acquired through this referral program. The name and e-mail address are used for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. The e-mail will include a unique code that is used for receiving the referral discount and for tracking the success of our referral program.   
  
Return to the top  
**Use of your Personal Information**  
  
We use personal information for order processing and customer support. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers or e-mail address on-line for order processing will receive telephone or e-mail contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. 

The information we collect is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

This site utilizes a third party to process and authorize credit card information. This third party does not use the information it is provided for promotional purposes. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information if required by law and/or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.   
  
Return to the top  
**Access to your Personal Information**  
  
Upon request we provide site visitors with access to financial information (e.g., credit card account information) that we maintain about them, unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them, a description of information that we maintain about them. 

Consumers can access this information by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address. 

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, financial information, unique identifiers, transaction information, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to the site. 

Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, or writing to us at the above address. Consumers can expect a response to such a request after no more than 10 working days.   
  
Return to the top  
**Security of your Personal Information**  
We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.   
Return to the top  
**Use of Cookies**  
  
We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart. 

We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals.   
  
Return to the top  
**Collection of Children's Personal Information**  
We do not knowingly collect or store any personal information from children.  
Return to the top  
**Joint or Co-Branded Products**  
  
Examples of current businesses that we may offer joint or co-branded products are Freescale Semiconductor Inc.

We do not exchange or share consumers' personal information with our joint or CO-branded affiliates.   
  
Return to the top  
**Enforcement of this Privacy Policy**  
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.   
Return to the top  
**Changes to this Statement**  
We may occasionally update or make changes to this privacy statement. We take your privacy seriously and will not adjust our policy to intentionally compromise your personal information. The "last updated" date at the top of the statement will reflect the last date at which the changes were made. Additionally, we may post notices regarding policy changes on the homepage or other pages on our website. We encourage you to check back periodically to review any changes to the policy that may have been made.   
Return to the top
